{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz --Resolutions-- ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"Image_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_189","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1. What is the first priority when considering security resolutions and best practices at work? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Brushing up on how to notice Phishing attempts ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Brushing up on how to notice Phishing attempts\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Keeping your device with you or locked at your workstation ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Keeping your device with you or locked at your workstation\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24884","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24888","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Personal physical security ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24884_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Personal physical security\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24942","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24946","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Protecting confidential information and the clean desk policy ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24942_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Protecting confidential information and the clean desk policy\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer: C  While all of these are great to consider as best practices, your personal security always takes precedence over information security. Types of security to keep us safe include CCTV surveillance, security guards, protective barriers, locks, access control protocols, and alarms. If you notice a discrepancy in any of these measures, ensure you notify the proper authority.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: C  While all of these are great to consider as best practices, your personal security always takes precedence over information security. Types of security to keep us safe include CCTV surveillance, security guards, protective barriers, locks, access control protocols, and alarms. If you notice a discrepancy in any of these measures, ensure you notify the proper authority.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_189","si12349","si12364","si12386","si24888","si24946","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1. What is the first priority when considering security resolutions and best practices at work?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_190","roles":{}},{"id":"si22070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_714","roles":{}},{"id":"si21978","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_698","title":"2. What is the most neglected security best practice in the workplace ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_704","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_705","title":"Classifying data based on its sensitivity ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_394","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Classifying data based on its sensitivity\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22000","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_706","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_707","title":"Updating user passwords ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22000_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_395","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Updating user passwords\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24737","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24741","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Frequently reviewing data available to all staff  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24737_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Frequently reviewing data available to all staff \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24752","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24756","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Conducting regular asset inventory ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24752_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Conducting regular asset inventory\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_713","roles":{}},{"id":"si22092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_103","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_104","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_105","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_106","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22162","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22186","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22234","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_710","title":"Correct - Answer: A  All of these important security practices are amongst the most neglected, however, only 64% of organizations classify data based on its level of sensitivity. Do you work with sensitive information? Perhaps a good resolution is to bring any unclassified sensitive information to the attention of your superior.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_711","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A  All of these important security practices are amongst the most neglected, however, only 64% of organizations classify data based on its level of sensitivity. Do you work with sensitive information? Perhaps a good resolution is to bring any unclassified sensitive information to the attention of your superior.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22058","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_712","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22259","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_190","si21978","si21993","si22004","si24741","si24756","si22092","si22110","si22132","si22150","si22162","si22174","si22186","si22198","si22210","si22222","si22234","si22246","si22058"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22259"},"question":{"interactionId":"21958","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. What is the most neglected security best practice in the workplace\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_191","roles":{}},{"id":"si22393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","roles":{}},{"id":"si22301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"3. A great New Year’s resolution is to back up your data at least once per week. How many people back up their personal data at least once per month? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"37% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_397","roles":{"answer":{"title":"37%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"56% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_398","roles":{"answer":{"title":"56%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24961","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"73% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24957_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"73%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24976","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"92% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24972_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"92%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","roles":{}},{"id":"si22415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"Correct - Answer: C  Surprisingly, 73% of consumers and 86% of businesses back up their data at least once per month; it is recommended to back up your personal data once per week and business data daily. World Backup Day is March 31st, take the pledge! Read more here:http://www.worldbackupday.com/en/  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: C  Surprisingly, 73% of consumers and 86% of businesses back up their data at least once per month; it is recommended to back up your personal data once per week and business data daily. World Backup Day is March 31st, take the pledge! Read more here: http://www.worldbackupday.com/en/  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_191","si22301","si22316","si22327","si24961","si24976","si22415","si22433","si22455","si22473","si22485","si22497","si22509","si22521","si22533","si22545","si22557","si22569","si22381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22582"},"question":{"interactionId":"22281","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3. A great New Year’s resolution is to back up your data at least once per week. How many people back up their personal data at least once per month?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_192","roles":{}},{"id":"si22716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","roles":{}},{"id":"si22624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"4. The level of phishing websites has grown significantly in the third quarter of 2019. How many phishing websites have been discovered? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"98,265 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"98,265\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"138,328 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"138,328\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22657","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_730","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_731","title":"182,465 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22657_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"182,465\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22932","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"266,387 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22928_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"266,387\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","roles":{}},{"id":"si22738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"Correct -  Answer: D  According to the Anti-Phishing Working Group, the number of phishing websites discovered has risen 46% from second quarter reporting; it is the highest since 2016. Make it your resolution to stay vigilant against attacks, be suspicious of unsolicited emails or attachments.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: D  According to the Anti-Phishing Working Group, the number of phishing websites discovered has risen 46% from second quarter reporting; it is the highest since 2016. Make it your resolution to stay vigilant against attacks, be suspicious of unsolicited emails or attachments.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22905","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_192","si22624","si22639","si22650","si22661","si22932","si22738","si22756","si22778","si22796","si22808","si22820","si22832","si22844","si22856","si22868","si22880","si22892","si22704"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22905"},"question":{"interactionId":"22604","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. The level of phishing websites has grown significantly in the third quarter of 2019. How many phishing websites have been discovered?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_193","roles":{}},{"id":"si23144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_749","roles":{}},{"id":"si23041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_701","title":"5.  Many people will make a resolution to be more secure when mobile working. What are some of the things you should do (click all that apply)? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_737","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_738","title":"Always keep your laptop with you when in transit ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23056","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23333q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23052_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Always keep your laptop with you when in transit\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":3}}}},{"id":"si23063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_739","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_740","title":"Use DTS or VPN when connecting to the network  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23067","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23333q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23063_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use DTS or VPN when connecting to the network \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":3}}}},{"id":"si23074","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_741","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23078","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_742","title":"Take your laptop to the nearest coffee shop to use their Wi-Fi ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23078","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23333q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23074_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Take your laptop to the nearest coffee shop to use their Wi-Fi\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23085","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_743","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_744","title":"Ask your family members to watch your computer when away from your desk ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23089","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23333q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23085_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ask your family members to watch your computer when away from your desk\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24987","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24991","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ensure your home Wi-Fi router has WEP encryption ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24991","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23333q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si24987_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensure your home Wi-Fi router has WEP encryption\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25002","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25006","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Be sure you change your router’s default password ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25006","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide23333q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si25002_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Be sure you change your router’s default password\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":4}}}},{"id":"si23138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_748","roles":{}},{"id":"si23166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_115","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23184","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_116","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_117","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_118","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23236","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23260","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23296","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_745","title":"Correct - Answer: A,B,F  Try to avoid logging onto the government network at a Wi-Fi coffee shop (if you do, ensure you use DTS or VPN). Your computer should be locked when you are away from your desk whether at home or at work. WEP encryption is vulnerable, WPA2 is the more secure encryption for your home router.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_746","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: A,B,F  Try to avoid logging onto the government network at a Wi-Fi coffee shop (if you do, ensure you use DTS or VPN). Your computer should be locked when you are away from your desk whether at home or at work. WEP encryption is vulnerable, WPA2 is the more secure encryption for your home router.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_747","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23333","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_193","si23041","si23056","si23067","si23078","si23089","si24991","si25006","si23166","si23184","si23206","si23224","si23236","si23248","si23260","si23272","si23284","si23296","si23308","si23320","si23132"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23333"},"question":{"interactionId":"23021","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  Many people will make a resolution to be more secure when mobile working. What are some of the things you should do (click all that apply)?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","F"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_194","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_194","roles":{}},{"id":"si23482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","roles":{}},{"id":"si23379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"6.  With the loss of personal information, most people who sign up for applications and services thoroughly read their terms and conditions. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","roles":{}},{"id":"si23504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23544","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  According to a recent study, 91% of adults and 97% of young adults consent  to terms and services without reading them. A Georgia high school teacher won $10,000 by reading the fine print of her travel insurance policy (hidden there by the company). Resolve to know what you are agreeing to in 2020.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  B  According to a recent study, 91% of adults and 97% of young adults consent  to terms and services without reading them. A Georgia high school teacher won $10,000 by reading the fine print of her travel insurance policy (hidden there by the company). Resolve to know what you are agreeing to in 2020.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_194","si23379","si23394","si23405","si23504","si23522","si23544","si23562","si23574","si23586","si23598","si23610","si23622","si23634","si23646","si23658","si23470"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23671"},"question":{"interactionId":"23359","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  With the loss of personal information, most people who sign up for applications and services thoroughly read their terms and conditions.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_195","roles":{}},{"id":"si23820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","roles":{}},{"id":"si23717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"7.  When using social media, you should resolve to: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"Update your friends only to those you know ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_411","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Update your friends only to those you know\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"Remove personal information  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_412","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Remove personal information \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_769","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"Post pictures only when you return from vacation ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23750_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"399_413","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Post pictures only when you return from vacation\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24834","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review privacy settings at least once per year ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24830_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Review privacy settings at least once per year\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25035","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25039","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25035_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","roles":{}},{"id":"si23842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"Correct - Answer:  E  Social Media is like being in the middle of a crowd - many people have intimate information exposed to ‘friends of friends of friends’ (ensure you know everyone on your list). Posting pictures while on vacation can expose GPS information and let everyone know exactly where you are or, most importantly, where you aren’t (home, in your hotel room, etc.). Resolve to use discretion on your social media accounts - keep your location and private information private.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer:  E  Social Media is like being in the middle of a crowd - many people have intimate information exposed to ‘friends of friends of friends’ (ensure you know everyone on your list). Posting pictures while on vacation can expose GPS information and let everyone know exactly where you are or, most importantly, where you aren’t (home, in your hotel room, etc.). Resolve to use discretion on your social media accounts - keep your location and private information private.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24009","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_195","si23717","si23732","si23743","si23754","si24834","si25039","si23842","si23860","si23882","si23900","si23912","si23924","si23936","si23948","si23960","si23972","si23984","si23996","si23808"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24009"},"question":{"interactionId":"23697","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  When using social media, you should resolve to:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_199","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_199","roles":{}},{"id":"si25203","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_815","roles":{}},{"id":"si25089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_793","title":"8.  It is a good idea to subscribe to the Security News Digest to keep up-to-date on current technology, breaches and security news. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_801","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_802","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25100_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_423","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_803","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_804","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25111_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_424","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_814","roles":{}},{"id":"si25225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_132","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_133","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25265","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_134","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_135","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25295","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25307","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25331","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25343","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25355","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25367","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25379","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25167","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_811","title":"Correct - Answer:  A  Make a solid resolution to sign up for the Security News Digest, you’ll be glad you did. :)  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_812","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer:  A  Make a solid resolution to sign up for the Security News Digest, you’ll be glad you did. :)  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_813","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25392","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_199","si25089","si25104","si25115","si25225","si25243","si25265","si25283","si25295","si25307","si25319","si25331","si25343","si25355","si25367","si25379","si25191"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25392"},"question":{"interactionId":"25069","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8.  It is a good idea to subscribe to the Security News Digest to keep up-to-date on current technology, breaches and security news.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_198","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298","Image_198"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Jan2020Quiz","class":"project","title":"Jan2020Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide12483","Slide22259","Slide22582","Slide22905","Slide23333","Slide23671","Slide24009","Slide25392","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide22259q1","Slide22582q2","Slide22905q3","Slide23333q4","Slide23671q5","Slide24009q6","Slide25392q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide22259","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide22582","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide22905","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide23333","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide23671","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide24009","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide25392","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}